Guide to the Michael Ellis Papers, 1937-1985 CTC.1977.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Addition, 1960-1981; XIV.
  - Kentwood Company, 1960-1981; 1.
    The series is organized into four parts: the original Limited Partnership Agreement (1 folder), Statements of Company Condition, 1963-1981 (1 folder), correspondence, chiefly regarding location of partners who had moved, 1971-82 (2 folders), and the chronological history of the company, 1960-81, including individual partner and company tax returns (United States, New York State, and New York City), bank statements, and royalty statements (41 folders).
    - Original Theatrical Partnership Agreement, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Statements of Company Condition, 1963-1981 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1982 (Box 45, Folder 3-4)
    - Tax returns, 1961 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Tax returns - Partners' Share List, 1963-1964 (Box 45, Folder 6-7)
    - Partners' Share List - Miscellaneous, 1966-1969 (Box 45, Folder 8-11)
    - Partners' Share List - Miscellaneous, 1970-1972 (Box 46, Folder 1-3)
    - Individual partner tax returns, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Partners' Share List - Bank statements and miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Individual partners' tax returns, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Partners' Share List - Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Cancelled checks and royalty statements, 1973-1975 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Partners' Share List - Tax returns and miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Bank statements, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Individual partners' tax returns, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Check stubs, 1971-1975 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Tax returns and bank statements, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Partners' Share List - Tax returns and miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Individual partners' tax returns, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Partner's Share List - Returned partner tax forms and miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Individual partners' tax returns, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Partners' Share List - Returned partner tax forms and miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Individual partners' tax returns, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Partners' Share List - Bank and royalty statements, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Returned partner tax forms and distribution checks, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Individual partner tax return - Bank statements and cancelled checks, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Partners' Share List - Tax forms, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Individual partner's tax returns, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Partnership Identification Data form - Tax information and miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Tax forms - Partnership Identification Data form and financial statements, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Cancelled checks, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Individual partner tax returns, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Company worksheets - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Individual partner tax returns, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Copy of the Theatrical Limited Partnership Agreement - Partners' Share List and miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Individual partner tax returns, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Returned partner tax forms and distribution checks, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Cello Company, 1968-1981; 2.
    Organized similarly as the Kentwood Company subseries, except that the original Limited Partnership Agreement is missing, including: Statements of Company Condition, 1968-78 (1 folder), correspondence, 1978-83 (2 folders), chronological history of the company, 1968-81 (27 folders).
    - Statements of Company Condition, 1968-1978 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1983 (Box 52, Folder 5-6)
    - Tax forms - Cancelled checks and other statements, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Partners' Share List - Tax materials and bank statements, 1969-1970 (Box 52, Folder 8-9)
    - Partners' Share List - Tax materials and bank statements, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Individual partners' tax returns, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Partners' Share List - Bank and royalty statements, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Returned partner tax forms, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Individual partners' tax returns, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Partners' Share List - Tax forms and statements, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Returned partner tax forms, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Individual partners' tax returns, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Returned partner tax forms - Cancelled / blank checks, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Individual partners' tax returns, 1975-1976 (Box 53, Folder 3-4)
    - Tax forms and financial statements, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Individual partners' tax returns, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Returned partner tax forms - Statements and correspondence, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Individual partners' tax returns, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Tax returns - Returned partner tax forms and financial statements, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Individual partners' tax returns, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Individual partners' tax returns, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Partnership Identification Data form - Financial statements and correspondence, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Individual partners' tax returns, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Partnership Identification Data form - Tax returns and royalty statements, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Individual partners' tax returns, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Final Partnership Identification Data form - Tax returns and royalty statements, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Checkbook of stubs and unused checks, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 3)